Gabriel Rimmon

+972 (55) 939-9975 | gxrimn@gmail.com | Tel Aviv

Summary

Full-stack Software Engineer with 5 years professional experience. I have a specialty in IoT cloud-based web applications as consultant for many organizations and industries including healthcare and manufacturing. Currently a Data Science Fellow at Israel Tech Challenge.

Professional Experience

2019 Software Engineer

Innoviz

Rosh Ha'ayin, Israel

 Responsible for autonomous vehicle trip data collection, transformation, and storage, along with a full Angular7 front-end for visualization and export of rosbag data

2018 Software Engineer II

BlueMetal Architects Boston, MA

- Full-stack developer Microsoft Azure Cloud/IoT applications, working with a variety of different projects and technologies in a variety of different industries
- Front-end lead on a security camera IoT troubleshoot web app for Avigilon (react.js/Redux)
- Web services lead on 2 IoT dashboard webapps in the manufacturing and foodservice industries (ASP.NET Core)

2015-2017 Software Engineer I

BlueMetal Architects Boston, MA

- Web services consultant for a big data/predictive analytics project for Stewart Healthcare
- Lead mobile developer for an IoT mobile application for Otis Elevator Company (iOS, swift)
- Company-wide MVP award Q2 2017

2013-2015 Software Developer

Epic Systems

Madison, WI

- Developed, enhanced, & maintained various features of infrastructure & data trending tools of Ambulatory application
- Certified in VB / Cache programming and Ambulatory Applications
- Gained significant knowledge of US healthcare industry its regulations

Education

2018-2019 Israel Tech Challenge Fellows - five-month full-time training course in collaboration with leading tech companies, which qualifies talented STEM BSc/MSc graduates as professional Data Scientists. Main focus is hands-on experience and skill-set in Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Computer Vision, and more, through exercises, self-led learning, and teamwork

2013 B.A. Computer Science - Boston University

- Dean's List 2013
- Courses in Networks, Databases, Computer Graphics, Information Security, Computer Systems, Algorithms

Technical Skills

Python, C# ASP.NET (Core), Azure Resource Management, Javascript (React.js/Redux), Java, C, C++, SQL, Docker, Spark, Git, Linux, sklearn, Keras, Tensorflow.

Data Science topics: Exploration, modeling, feature engineering, dimensionality reduction, regularization techniques and model tuning, clustering, neural networks, optimization, computer vision, NLP, serving model. Software development skills: Software architecture, cloud resource management (IoT specialty), and front-end and web service development, Agile/Scrum

Additional Information

Native English speaker, Intermediate-level Hebrew